export const Questions = [
    {
        prompt: "1. What does PHP stand for?",
        optionA: "Hypertext Preprocessor",
        optionB: "Hypertext Programming",
        optionC: "Hypertext Preprogramming",
        optionD: "Hometext Preprocessor",
        answer: "A",
    },
    {
        prompt: "2. What is a streaming platform?",
        optionA: "Twitter",
        optionB: "Twitch",
        optionC: "Google",
        optionD: "Rabinhood",
        answer: "B",
    },
    {
        prompt: "3. What does CSS stand for?",
        optionA: "Common Style Sheet",
        optionB: "Colorful Style Sheet",
        optionC: "Computer Style Sheet",
        optionD: "Cascading Style Sheet",
        answer: "D",
    },
    {
        prompt: "4. Who founded Apple Computer?",
        optionA: "Stephen Fry",
        optionB: "Bill Gates",
        optionC: "Steve Jobs",
        optionD: "Stephen Hawking",
        answer: "C",
    },
    {
        prompt: "5. What does the Internet prefix WWW stand for?",
        optionA: "Wide Width Wickets",
        optionB: "World Wide Web",
        optionC: "Worldwide Weather",
        optionD: "Western Washington World",
        answer: "B",
    },
    {
        prompt: "6. Which of these is not a kind of computer?",
        optionA: "Apple",
        optionB: "Lenovo",
        optionC: "Toshiba",
        optionD: "Lada",
        answer: "D",
    },
    {
        prompt: "7. When was the DVD introduced?",
        optionA: "1970",
        optionB: "1990",
        optionC: "2000",
        optionD: "1995",
        answer: "D",
    },
    {
        prompt: "8. Which of these is not a telephone?",
        optionA: "Ipod",
        optionB: "Razr",
        optionC: "Blackberry",
        optionD: "Iphone",
        answer: "A",
    },
    {
        prompt: "9. Who is the maker of the iPhone?",
        optionA: "Microsoft",
        optionB: "IBM",
        optionC: "Apple",
        optionD: "Zenith",
        answer: "C",
    },
    {
        prompt: "10. What is the name for a computer pointing device?",
        optionA: "A Mouse",
        optionB: "Sound Card",
        optionC: "Ram",
        optionD: "Monitor",
        answer: "A",
    },
];